-这位是  -梅格
- She's... - Meg.
她是个恶魔  萨姆
She's a demon, Sam.
记得我吗  我可记得你哦  小天使
Remember me? I sure remember you, Clarence.
我从批萨男那里学来的
I learned that from the pizza man.
她在逃命  就是说  你们在躲克劳力
She's running. Which means you're running from Crowley.
我叫娜奥米  我们救了你
My name is Naomi. We rescued you.
卡西迪奥  他们在控制我们
They're controlling us, Castiel!
杀了他  这是命令
Kill him! This is a direct order!
我刚刚做了什么
What did I just do?
你告诉温彻斯特兄弟萨曼德里奥
You tell the Winchesters that Samandriel had been...
变节了
Compromised.
-你只得  -自卫
- You acted in... - Self-defense.
小卡  你还好吧
Cass, you okay?
还有一块碑  就是说还有神之语
There's another tablet? So, another word of God.
卡西迪奥  天使石碑
The angel tablet, Castiel.
克劳力知道了
Crowley knows.
上帝建立了一系列测试
God built a series of tests.
等你都完成了  就可以去关门了
When you've done all three, you can slam the gates of hell.
萨姆  我没能通过测试
Sam, I didn't pass the test.
但是我通过了  剩下的都让我来
But I did. And I'm doing the rest of them.
小卡  你在听吗
Cass, you got your ears on?
照顾一下我弟弟  好吗
You keep a lookout for my little brother, okay?
如今
不  小卡  不要
No, Cass. No!
不  小卡  求你
No, Cass, don't. Please.
毫无迟疑
No hesitation.
干净利落
Quick. Brutal.
一切都恢复正常了
Everything's back in order.
真不容易
Finally.
你终于准备好了
You're ready.
凶鬼恶灵
第八季 第十七集
再见  陌生人
这是什么啊
What the hell is this?
命运之矛
Spear of destiny?
算什么  上帝的牙签吗
What is this -- God's toothpick?
我说这些混蛋就不能
You know, would it have killed these asshats
用点人看得懂的字做标签吗
to label these boxes in something other than hieroglyphics?
真受不了
It's ridiculous.
听见了没啊
Hey. You listening to me?
听见了
Yeah.
挺不错的
It's, uh... fascinating stuff.
你应该
You should probably, uh,
都写进你的记录以便存档
write it all down in your journal for the archives, you know?
谢了  你真是帮了大忙
Yeah, thanks. You're a lot of help.
霍利戴医生  你没事吧
Hey, Doc Holliday, you all right over there?
十九世纪下半页美国西部一位投机商  枪手  也曾是牙医
没事
Uh, yeah.
我很好
Um... I'm fine.
呛到了
Just, uh, wrong pipe.
亚洲情色
不赖啊
Well, hello.
看来记录者也不都是呆子嘛
These men of letters weren't so boring after all.
你好啊
Konnichiwa.
快瞧瞧这个
Hey, check this out.
你有什么毛病啊
What is wrong with you?
我什么毛病
What's wrong with me?
开玩笑呢  这可是初版啊
You kidding me? This is a first edition, dude.
你知道这东西在易趣网上能卖多少钱吗
You know what this would go for on eBay?
不知道  怎么  你知道
No. Why? Do you?
不知道啊
No.
或许知道吧
Maybe.
闭嘴吧你
Shut up.
有发现吗
You find anything?
有
I did, yeah --
中西部地区上周发现多具尸体
Uh, dead bodies showing up all over the midwest last week.
印第安纳州  本顿  伊利诺伊州  丹尼森市
Benton, Indiana; Downers Grove, illinois;
密执根  诺维
uh, Novi, Michigan;
昨晚密苏里州  林肯泉也死人了
and then again last night in Lincoln Springs, Missouri.
这跟我们什么关系
And how is this us?
因为所有的死者均有严重灼伤
Because each of the victims had severe burns
眼睛周围  手和脚都有
around their eyes, hands, and feet,
手背有穿透伤
puncture wounds through the backs of their hands,
眼睛和内脏被液化
eyes and internal organs liquefied.
是我们的事
That sounds like us.
是啊
Yeah.
而且死者之间毫无关联
Also, no link between any of the victims.
一个地产商
Uh, one was a real-estate agent.
一个当地的历史学家
Another was a local historian.
昨晚死去的女人是个老师
Woman killed last night was a teacher.
山羊吸血怪吗
So, chupacabra.
怎么  控制不住发狂了吗
What do we got? Power tools gone rogue?
等等
Wait -- are we talking
这是《火魔战车》那种情况吗
a-a "Maximum overdrive" situation here?
史蒂芬・金导演的动作惊悚片  讲机器攻击人类  人类只得反抗
不知道
I don't know.
值得去瞧瞧
Worth a shot, though.
我去拿东西  我们五分钟后出发
I'll grab my gear. We should probably leave in five.
当然  除非你要多花点时间陪十月小姐
'less, of course, you need some more time with miss October.
什么
What?
是啊  十分钟吧
Yeah. Yeah, make it 10.
我们只想问几个关于你妻子的
We just have a few routine follow-up
常规后续问题
questions about your wife, sir.
她有仇家吗
Did she have any enemies?
安吗
Ann?
说实话  我想不出任何人会想伤害她
Honestly, I can't think of a soul who'd want to hurt her,
即使发生了那些事
even after everything that happened.
发生了哪些事
Everything that happened?
一周前安发生了些变化
About a week ago, something changed in Ann.
她很反常  很易怒
She was out of sorts, not herself at all.
怎么个易怒法
Out of sorts how?
我带你们去看吧
It'd be better if I show you.
她不睡
She stopped sleeping.
不吃
She stopped eating.
大半夜跑出去
She went out in the middle of the night,
也不知是去哪了
going God knows where.
我想跟她沟通
I tried to talk to her, but, uh...
可她只是喃喃自语
she would just mutter to herself.
说什么
About what?
跟什么果园有关
Something... about an orchard?
后来有一晚我跟上了她
Finally, I just followed her one night,
她去了操场
and she went to the playground.
就是小学这里
Over here -- the elementary school.
然后她开始挖
And she started digging.
她带着几个装满土的小袋子
She would leave with these little bags full of dirt.
挂在这儿
Hung them here.
这些袋子都代表了她在地上挖的洞
All these bags represent holes that she dug in the ground.
这些洞  有六英尺深吗
Were these holes, uh -- I don't know -- 6 feet deep?
不
No.
她一挖就几小时
She dug for hours.
完全不知道累
She never broke a sweat.
一直挖10到15英尺
Straight down 10, maybe 15 feet.
你还注意到其他事了吗
Did you notice anything else?
我没跟警察说
I didn't say anything to the cops
我不想让他们认为我疯了
'cause I didn't want them to think I was crazy.
安回家后
After Ann came home,
我来这儿跟她对质
I came down here to confront her,
她当时正打电话
and she was on the phone.
知道她在跟谁通话吗
Any idea who she was talking to?
不知道
No.
但我知道我看到了什么
But I know what I saw.
那不是我的安妮
And it wasn't my Annie.
我喊了她的名字  她的眼睛...
After I called her out, her eyes...
变成黑色的了
They turned black.
我知道  这一定是我想出来的
Now, I-I know I must have imagined it.
肯定是这样  但我出门了
I know I did. But I-I left.
我去了酒吧  大概多喝了两杯
I went to the bar, probably had too much to drink,
等我回来的时候
and by the time I came back...
我的安妮已经...
...my Annie was, uh...
我不该出去的
I should have stayed.
我该保护她的
I should have protected her.
我今天要搬去我姐姐家
I'm moving into my sister's place today.
我不能再待在这儿了
I can't be here anymore.
可以理解
Sure.
非常感谢你的配合
Well, um, thank you very much for your time.
我们深表哀悼
We're both very sorry for your loss.
有人在杀恶魔  真是太棒了
So, somebody's killing demons. Well, that is awesome.
我觉得我们该送花或者感谢卡
I feel like we should send a card or flowers.
哪种花的花语是"谢谢你杀恶魔"
What kind of flower says "Thanks for killing demons"?
但是谁在杀恶魔  又是为什么
Yeah, but who's killing demons? And why?
再者  被恶魔附身的人怎么还
And, by the way, since when does a demon possess someone,
突然变成了天才
then go all "Beautiful mind"
到处去挖土了
and -- and start digging in the dirt?
你觉得这对劲吗
Does any of this seem right to you?
我喜欢杀恶魔的部分  挺对劲的
I like the part about killing demons. That sounds right.
没问题
Sure.
好的
Of course.
非常感谢你的帮助
Well, thank you very much for all your help.
真是麻烦你了
I really appreciate the time.
好的  再见
All right. Bye.
地产商的妻子也说他行为古怪
So, real-estate guy's wife said he was acting weird.
历史学家的丈夫也这么说
Uh, historian's hubby said the same --
也是突然执迷古怪了起来
just got all obsessive and then weird.
但没人看到黑眼珠
No one saw any black eyes,
但是  无风不起浪嘛
but still, where there's smoke, you know...
不知道他们都在找什么啊
I wonder what they're all looking for.
温迪・赖斯是最后跟安说话的人
Well, Wendy Rice here was the last person to speak with Ann,
看看她会怎么说
so let's see if she can tell us.
林恩特工
Special agent Lynne.
这是我搭档坦迪特工
This is my partner, special agent Tandy.
我们想就安・莫顿问你几个问题
We'd like to ask you a few questions about Ann Morton.
当然了  请进吧
Uh, uh, uh, of course. Please come in.
那天她来电话之前我从没见过她
I had never met her before she called the other night.
她打电话是什么事
Now, why was she calling you?
她是想找一张城市最早的地图
She was looking to find an original map of the city.
她说要干什么用了吗
Did she say what for?
她没说  但是她提到了
Well, she -- she didn't, but she did mention
一片消失的果园
an -- an old orchard that had gone missing.
消失
Missing?
这座小镇曾被夷为平地
This -- this town was wiped from the earth
那是场百年不遇的洪水
by one of the river's 100-year floods.
现在的小镇是重建的
It was -- it was rebuilt.
但原始的记录都遗失了
But all the original records were -- were lost.
我是名博士候选人
I'm -- I'm a PhD candidate.
这是我的研究
And this -- this is my research.
我
I, uh...
我的论文是关于小镇的历史
my dissertation is -- is on the history of this town
它与地下铁路的联系
and, uh, its connection to the underground railroad
这一类的
and -- and -- and whatnot.
这些年  我研究的一部分就是
I've been working to re-create a map
重划一张地图
for years as part of my research,
而这里就是贾库比卡果园旧址
and this -- this is the old Jakubiak orchard there.
我昨天发现是在唐尼和邦德街街口
I found out yesterday it's where Downey meets Bond street.
安有说过她为什么要找
Now, did Ann say why she was looking
果园的旧址了吗
for the site of an old orchard?
没有
No.
我们约好见面  她却没有来
We -- we set a time to meet, and she never showed.
然后我就在报纸上看到了
Then I read about her in the paper.
真惨啊
It's just tragic.
不过安的助手今早来电话了
Ann's assistant called this morning, though,
问地图是否还在我手里
asking if I still had the map.
助手
Assistant?
大概就是他了
That's probably him.
或许他能帮你们
Maybe he can help.
你们是...
Oh. Are -- are you --
这个放在你肩上
Put this on your shoulder.
我没事
I'm fine.
还有个恶魔跑了
The other demon escaped.
我抓到的那个我放在恶魔陷阱里了
I bound the one I caught in a devil's trap.
我这就去审问她
I'm gonna interrogate it now.
等等  小卡
Wait a second. Cass.
你先回答我们几个问题吧
How about you answer some questions first?
比如  你最近都去哪了
Like, where the hell have you been?
你听到我了  是吗
You heard me, didn't you?
你向他祈祷了吗
You prayed to him?
对  我听到了
Yes, I heard you.
但我来不是为了那个
But that's not why I'm here.
我在四处猎恶魔
I've been hunting demons.
这是你干的
So this is you.
为什么
Why?
我要怎么说
What should I tell them?
说实话
The truth.
至少是大部分事实
Most of it, anyway.
或许他们能帮我们更近一步
Maybe they can get us closer.
我在到处找恶魔石碑的另一半
I've been searching for the other half of the demon tablet.
不带我们吗
Without us?
我是想帮忙  迪恩
I've been trying to help, Dean.
在搜寻过程中
And in my search,
我发现克劳力派恶魔到处找路西法的地宫
I uncovered that Crowley has sent out demons to find Lucifer's crypts.
路西法的地宫
Lucifer had crypts?
而且还有几十个
Dozens of them, apparently.
那他们到处挖土是怎么回事
But why the storage wars?
他们到底在找什么
I mean, what the hell are they all looking for?
如果他们知道全部实情会更好
It would be more helpful if they knew everything.
-我们不能信任他们  -但是
- They cannot be trusted. - But --
撒谎  卡西迪奥
Lie, Castiel.
告诉我们说好的故事
Tell them what we discussed.
他们在找一张羊皮纸
They're looking for a parchment
好破解克劳力手里的恶魔石碑
that would allow them to decipher Crowley's half of the demon tablet
这样就不需要先知了
without a prophet.
恶魔解码器
A demonic decoder ring?
被克劳力拿到
In Crowley's hands?
太棒了
Awesome.
地宫的位置早已失传
The crypts were, uh, lost over time.
只有那些路西法的亲信才知道
Only those closest to Lucifer knew their whereabouts.
那克劳力怎么找到的
Then how did Crowley find them?
他的恶魔附身了一些
His demons have been possessing locals
知道特定事情的当地人
who may have some special knowledge.
所以安的屋里会布置成那样
That would explain the crazy room at Ann's house.
但他们怎么知道该去哪找呢
But how did they know where to start looking in the first place?
不知道
I don't know.
我希望厨房里那个发型特异的恶魔
I'm hoping the strange-haired demon in the kitchen
比我审过的其他恶魔能知道的更多
is more knowledgeable than the others I interrogated.
真是混蛋版的小卡
Well, he puts the "ass" in "Cass," Huh?
他绝对有问题
He's definitely off.
有问题
Off?
他从炼狱回来就没正常过
He hasn't been right since he got back from purgatory.
而且我们还不知道他到底怎么出来的
We still don't know how he got out of there.
可话说回来  迪恩
I don't know, Dean.
既然他这么不对劲  你怎么还向他祈祷
If he's so sketchy, then why were you praying to him?
我能听到你们说话
You know, I can hear you both.
我可是天使啊
I am a celestial being.
萨姆和迪恩・温彻斯特
Sam and Dean Winchester.
她对你们俩很感兴趣呢
Oh, the thoughts she had about you two.
尤其是你  萨姆
Mostly you, Sam.
没办法
What can I say?
她就是喜欢嫩的
She has a thing for smutton chops.
行了  你个二货
All right, you douchebag, listen --
地宫的事是谁告诉你的
Who told you about the crypts?
天使不是唱红脸的吗
I thought angels were supposed to be the good cops.
等等  住手
Wait! Stop!
住手
Stop!!
我们有人质
We have a hostage!
克劳力的走狗
It's one of Crowley's pets.
她住在州际公路边的莫里旅馆
She's at the Murray hotel, down by the interstate.
她知道镇上的地宫都埋在了哪
She knows the towns where all the crypts are buried.
她当年看到过
She saw them all back in the day.
羊皮纸的事也是她说的吗
And she told you about the parchment?
什么羊皮纸
What parchment?!
他可不是唯一唱白脸的
Think he's the only bad cop in this room?
被骗我了
Stop lying!
我们知道你们到底想找什么
We know what you're really looking for.
不
No.
我说了  我们在找
I am telling you, we're looking...
杀了她
Kill it!
找
...for
小卡
Cass!
你这是干什么
What the hell was that?!
我们要知道的都问出来了
It told us what we needed.
不  没有  你不能
No, she didn't! You can't just --
我独自一人搜寻
I started this hunt without you
就是不想被人拖后腿
because I didn't want anything to slow me down.
我们得马上去旅馆
We have to get to the motel now.
等等
Hold on a second --
-小卡  -小卡
- Cass! - Cass? Cass?
该死  快走
Damn it. Go. Go. Go.
那儿呢
There. There.
多谢等我们了
Thanks for waiting.
人质在那间屋里
The hostage is in there.
你做突击队是不是矮了点
Aren't you a little short for a stormtrooper?
我得问问
So, I got to ask. Um...
头发是怎么回事
What's up with the hair?
怎么了
What?
多谢你注意到了  迪恩
Aww. Thanks for noticing, Dean.
但这是克劳力弄的
But this wasn't my idea. It was Crowley's.
也是我想一刀插他脸上的另一条理由
And it's just another reason I want to stab him in the face.
等等
Wait a second.
你把路西法地宫的位置都告诉克劳力了
You've been telling Crowley the location of Lucifer's crypts.
没办法啊
What can I say?
我只想让他偶尔暂停对我的折磨
I needed a break from the constant torture.
我跟黄眼恶魔混的时候的确都去过
And I did visit them all during my time with yellow eyes.
别担心
But don't worry.
要紧的我都没说呢
I haven't exactly been giving them the Glengarry leads.
你对他们撒谎了
You mean you've been lying to them?
我给了个大概位置
I just get them in the ballpark.
过了这么久  肯定有所变化
Enough time's passed and enough's changed
他们也信了
That they bought it.
为什么撒谎
Why lie?
拖延时间啊  傻帽
Buy myself some time, dummy.
想办法逃脱
Try to find a way to get free.
那么  死了那么多无辜的人
Wait -- so... A bunch of innocent people died
就是为了让你拖延时间吗
so you could... buy yourself some time?
我是梅格  我是个恶魔
Hi. I'm Meg. I'm a demon.
他们找到了什么
So, what have they found?
什么都没有
Bupkis.
每次打开地宫都是一无所获
Every crypt's been one Al Capone's vault after another.
而且还有人发现了他们
And on top of that, someone kept picking up the trail
把他们杀掉了
and icing demons.
我猜是你吧  卡西迪奥
I'm guessing that was you, Castiel.
但克劳力还是继续派人
But Crowley just keeps sending more.
他决心要...
He's hell-bent on...
她会把实情说出来的
She's gonna tell them the truth.
我要杀了她吗
Do I have to kill her?
但她也知道地宫的位置
She does know the location of the crypts.
但是跟恶魔合作是不检点的
But working with a demon is...unclean.
我们可以像克劳力那样利用她
Well, we could use her -- as Crowley did.
好的
Agreed.
找到天使石碑
...finding that angel tablet.
你说什么
Wait a second.
"天使石碑"
Did you just say "Angel tablet"?
我现在知道克劳力为什么喊你"小鹿"了
You know, I get why Crowley calls you "Moose" Now.
对  "天使石碑"
Yes -- "Angel tablet."
克劳力发现石碑本来在路西法手里
Crowley found out Lucifer had it,
认定它一定藏在哪个地宫里
figures it's stashed in a crypt.
这我之前也不知道
Well, this is news to me, as well.
我审过的恶魔
Demons I interrogated,
一定都没说实话
they must have been lying about their true intentions.
是吗
Really?
我看到你之前是怎么对付那个恶魔的
'cause I saw you "Zero dark thirty" that demon.
你可很会逼供呢
You were more than persuasive.
你们都没抓住重点
You're both missing the point.
我撒了谎
I lied to them,
所以他们一直都没找对地方
which means they're digging in the wrong place.
但不会很久了  他们很快就会回来
But not for long. They'll be back here soon.
谁想逃
So, who's up for fleeing?
她说得对  我们得赶在他们之前找到地宫
She's right. We need to find those crypts before they do.
梅格  只有你去过
Meg, you're the only one who's been there.
我们需要你帮助
We need your help.
你们哪个傻帽有地图吗
Any of you dummies got a map?
那儿  地宫就在那儿
There. That's where the crypt was.
现在是什么
What's there now?
我长得像谷歌地图吗
Do I look like google to you?
想当年这些楼都不存在呢
None of these buildings were here way back in the day.
自己去查吧  天才
Figure it out, genius.
这里有酒吗
Is there any booze in this dump?
他撒谎了
He lied to us.
或许吧  但我能理解
Yeah, maybe. I can kind of understand why.
那可是天使石碑啊
I mean, an angel tablet?
如果恶魔石碑能关上地狱大门
If the demon tablet can shut the gates of hell,
天使石碑会有什么威力
what can the angel tablet do?
这些伤口都溃烂了
These wounds have festered.
你可真会哄女人啊
You really do know how to make a girl's nethers quiver, don't you?
我的确知道要怎么做
I am aware of how to do that.
但是一般跟清理伤口无关
Although it doesn't usually involve cleaning wounds.
为什么对我这么好  小天使
Why are you so sweet on me, Clarence?
我不知道
I don't know.
我倒现在也不知道你为什么那么叫我
And I still don't know who Clarence is.
克拉伦斯是一部老电影中的天使
你去看个电影或者读本书能死啊
Would it kill you to watch a movie, read a book?
电影不至于
A movie, no.
但是如果是一本特定的咒语书
But a book with the proper spells --
理论上讲的确能让我死掉
Yeah, it could, theoretically, kill me.
你不说话的时候更可爱一些
You know, you're much cuter when you're shutting up.
你现在是什么样的小卡
So, which Cass are you now?
出厂设置还是疯癫版的
Original make and model or crazy town?
我就是我
I'm just me.
你脑子又正常了吗
So, your noodle's back in order?
我的脑子都记起来了
Yeah, my...noodle remembers everything.
脑子应该挺不错的
I think it's a pretty good noodle.
是嘛
Really?
什么都记得吗
You remember everything?
如果你是指披萨男
If you're referring to the pizza man...
是的  那个我也记得
Yes, I remember the pizza man.
而且是段愉快的记忆
And it's a good memory.
查到了
Here goes.
好了
All right.
从这上面看
According to this,
地宫应该在一栋废楼下面
the crypt has to be below an abandoned building.
太好了
Good times.
你觉得我们能相信他俩吗
You really think we can trust, uh, Meg-stiel?
不能
No.
但我们又能怎么样
But what choice do we have?
你怀念天启吗
You ever miss the Apocalypse?
不  我为什么要怀念呢
No. Why would I miss the end of times?
我怀念那时的单纯
I miss the simplicity.
我那时很坏  你很好
I was bad. You were good.
生活轻松一些
Life was easier.
现在一切都那么复杂
Now it's all so messy.
我似乎挺好  这样很不好
I'm kind of good, which sucks.
你似乎有点坏
And you're kind of bad --
这倒是挺性感的
Which is actually all manner of hot.
我们安然度过这次
We survive this...
我要点些匹萨
I'm gonna order some pizza
然后我们把家具挪挪位置
and we're gonna move some furniture around.
你明白吗
You understand?
不  我
No, I-I --
等下  其实
Wait -- actually...
是的  我
Yes, I --
好了  出发吧  驴友们
All right. Let's roll, campers.
先生
Sir?
我把那里从上到下找了个遍
I, uh, searched the site top to bottom.
是空的
It's empty.
不  那里没有地宫
No, there's no crypt there.
还有...不仅如此
And, uh, that's not all.
先生  现在只剩我一人了
It's just me now, sir.
我
I, um...
我们可能弄丢了梅格
We may have lost Meg.
先生
Sir?
喂  先生
Hello, sir?
把话说清楚
Just to be clear...
你找不到一个地洞
...you can't find a hole in the ground...
你的帮手不幸早死
Your coworkers have met with an untimely demise...
而你弄丢了我最喜欢的磨牙玩具
...and you've lost my favorite chew toy.
漂亮
Brilliant.
那句老话怎么说来着
What's that old expression?
"如果你想把事情做好"
"If you want something done right..."
什么  什么的
...blah, blah, blah.
就是这里
So, this is it.
在地下吗
Basement?
好吧  我和小卡进去
All right, Cass and I will head in
一探究竟
and get our Indiana Jones on.
萨姆  你和梅格待在外面
Sam, you stay outside with Meg.
-什么  -我们能行
- What? - We got this.
你说什么呢  迪恩
What are you talking about, Dean?
我才不会让你一个人进去
I'm not letting you go in there alone.
-他不是一个人  -我不是那个意思
- He won't be alone. - That's not what I mean.
梅格可以待在这里  帮我们把风
Meg can hang here, watch our backs.
怎么  现在你又相信梅格了
Oh, what? Now you trust Meg?
我都帮你们这么多了
Hey, I got you this far.
-闭嘴  -闭嘴  梅格
- Shut up. - Shut up, Meg.
迪恩
Dean --
萨姆  我看到垃圾桶里你沾血的手帕了
Sam, I saw your bloody rag in the trash can, okay?
-那不是...  -够了
- That wasn't... - Stop.
别说了
Just stop.
萨姆  我们不知道里面有什么
Sam, we don't know what's in there, okay?
之前你差点被一个恶魔干掉了
And you almost let a demon get the best of you back there.
-我没事  -不  你有事
- I'm fine. - No, you're not fine.
第一项测试开始你就很不好
You haven't been fine since the first trial.
所以我才叫来了小卡
That's why I called Cass.
测试
Trial?
-闭嘴  梅格  -闭嘴  梅格
- Shut up, Meg. - Shut up, Meg.
迪恩  我告诉你  我很好
Dean, I'm telling you -- I'm okay.
不  你不好
No, you're not.
萨姆
Sam...
你受到的伤害  我都无法治愈
You're damaged in ways even I can't heal.
迪恩说得对
Dean's right.
你应该待在这里  保护梅格
You should stay here and protect Meg.
我什么时候还需要保护了
Since when do I need protecting?
你被抓并虐待拷问了一年多
Since you were held captive and tortured for over a year.
有道理
Touche.
行了  我们很快回来
All right, we'll be back.
刚刚你说萨姆怎么了
Hey, what did you mean back there about Sam?
一言难尽
It's difficult to say.
那是亚原子层面的
It's something on the subatomic level
而他的电磁场
and his electromagnetic field --
简单点说  比尔・内[美著名科普专家]
Okay, bottom-line it for me, Bill Nye.
-致命吗  -不知道
- Is it lethal? - I don't know.
等下
Wait.
这里有风
There's a draft.
这后面有东西
There's something behind there.
后退
Stand back.
等下  我救过你们多少次了
Wait -- so I took how many bullets for you guys,
你们都没想来找我
and you didn't even look for me?
完全没想过吗
Like, once?
真英武
My hero.
测试和受伤什么的是怎么回事
What's with all the "Trial" and "Being damaged" crap?
恕我直言  但你并不是
Look, no disrespect, but you haven't exactly been
我们遇到的最值得信赖的人  梅格
the most, uh, trustworthy person in our lives, Meg.
你不打算告诉我吗
You're not gonna tell me?
不是吧
Seriously?
我还算不上是你的朋友吗
How am I not team Sam?
好吧
Fine.
不管是什么  你愿意为此而死吗
Whatever it is, you okay dying over it?
你不想说  好吧
You don't want to say, fine.
但是记住  我曾经附在你身上
But remember, I spent time in that walking corpse of yours.
我知道你的悲伤  想法还有感情
I know your sad, little thoughts and feelings.
真恐怖
That's creepy.
我记得是这样的
Here's what I remember.
内心深处  被你深深埋起来的那部分
Deep down, in parts you never let see the light of day,
你想过长久普通的生活
you want to live a long, normal life
远离我这种恐怖的老东西
away from creepy old things like me.
是的
I do.
我去年和一个人...
You know, I spent last year with...
一起度过
Someone, and, um...
现在我知道那是有可能的
...Now I know that's actually possible.
等等  你就这样度过去年的
Wait -- that's how you spent your last year?
和一个女人
With a chick?
真无聊
Lame.
我们安静地等他们吧
You know, how about we just wait quietly?
她叫什么名字
What was her name?
你连名字都不肯告诉我吗
You don't even trust me with a name?
我也是有感情的啊  萨姆
Cut me, do I not bleed, Sam?
有个女人居然能让你放弃猎魔
So, some chick actually got you off hunting, huh?
那真是个了不起的人
That's one rare creature.
告诉我
Tell me --
你是怎么遇见这个人的
How'd you meet this unicorn?
我找到了
I found it.
告诉温家兄弟地宫是空的
Tell the Winchester the crypt is empty.
然后你再回来
Then you can come back --
那东西抵御天使
It's warded against angels.
你可以再回来
Well, you can come back --
克劳力的爪牙还在镇上
Crowley's demons are still in town,
而且我们快没时间了
and we're running out of time.
我该怎么做
What should I do?
解决它
Handle it.
迪恩
Dean...
就是它
That's it.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
那是这里唯一抵御天使的东西
It's the only thing in here warded against angels.
赢两次  吃鸡肉[拉斯维加斯俗语]
Winner, winner, chicken dinner.
很好
Good.
把它交给我  我把它带回天堂
Hand it to me, and I'll take it to heaven.
不  我们要把它交给凯文让他翻译
No, we will take it to Kevin so he can translate.
好的  当然
Right. Of course.
我马上拿去给他
I'll take it to him right away.
别磨蹭了
No time to waste.
他离得挺近
Well, he's not that far.
我也一直想...去看看他
I've been meaning to... go check on him,
给他带些补给品
Bring him some supplies.
如果恶魔拿到了天使石碑
If the demons get their hands on the angel tablet,
他们会把我们一网打尽
they'll kill us all.
他们会摧毁天堂
They'll destroy heaven.
我可以说服迪恩
I can reason with Dean.
他是个好人
He's a good man.
杀了他
Kill him.
我可以给先知补充物资  迪恩
I can resupply the prophet, Dean.
不如...
You know, why don't, uh,
还是我和萨姆把石碑拿给他吧
why don't Sam and I take it over to him,
你继续去执行你的任务
and you can get back to your mission?
找到另一半恶魔石碑
Finding the other half of the demon tablet --
这才是首要任务  是不是
That is priority, isn't it?
我不能让你带走它  迪恩
I can't let you take that, Dean.
是不能还是不肯
Can't or won't?
两者都是
Both.
你是怎样从炼狱里出来的  小卡
How did you get out of purgatory, Cass?
一定还有别的方法
There has to be another way.
你已经演练过上千次了  卡西迪奥
You have done this a thousand times, Castiel.
你准备好了
You're ready.
杀了他
Kill him.
然后夺回石碑
Then take the tablet
把它带回天堂  它就该放这儿
and bring it home, where it belongs.
告诉我你是怎样逃出炼狱的
Just tell me how you got out of purgatory.
对我说次实话
Be honest with me --
算是你回来后的第一次
for the first time since you've been back --
石碑就给你
and this is yours.
等等  等一下
Wait -- h-hold on.
有一部分我没听懂
There's one part I don't understand.
你撞狗后停了车  为什么
You hit a dog and stopped. Why?
这整个故事  你就关心这个吗
That whole story, and that's your takeaway?
我听到其他的了
Oh, I heard the rest.
你爱上了一个特别的女人
You fell in love with a unicorn.
她很漂亮  然后越来越悲剧
It was beautiful, then sad, then sadder.
笑过  哭过  吐过
I laughed, I cried, I puked in my mouth a little.
老实讲  我能理解
And honestly, I kind of get it.
真的吗
Really?
有人来了
We've got company.
小卡
Cass.
小卡  我不知道你到底怎么回事
Cass, I don't know what the hell is wrong with you,
但如果你在那里  你能听到我说话
but if you're in there and you can hear me,
你不必这么做
you don't have to do this.
小卡
Cass!
这是不对的
This isn't right.
你明白石碑对我们的用处吗
Do you realize what that tablet can do for us?
我
I...
对天堂
For heaven?
我不会伤害迪恩
I won't hurt Dean.
会  你会的
Yes. You will.
你正在伤害他
You are.
小卡  抗争  这不是真正的你
Cass, fight this! This is not you!
与之抗争
Fight it!
你把我怎么了
What have you done to me?!
放松  卡西迪奥
Just relax, Castiel.
让你的肉身去做
Let your vessel do
你内心深知是正确的事
what you know deep down is the right thing.
你把我怎么了  娜奥米
What have you done to me, Naomi?
娜奥米是谁
Who's Naomi?!
我把你怎么了
What have I done to you?!
你知道现在外面是什么情况吗
Do you have any idea what it's like out there?
生灵涂炭  都是你一手造成
There's blood everywhere, and it's on your hands.
都是因为你对我们  对天堂做的一切
After everything you did -- to us, to heaven.
我治好了你  卡西迪奥
I fixed you, Castiel.
我治好了你
I fixed you!
小卡
Cass!
这雷应该是打给我的
I believe they're playing my song.
你想要它
You want it?
拿去吧
Take it!
但你得先杀了我
But you're gonna have to kill me first.
来啊  你个胆小鬼
Come on, you coward.
动手啊
Do it.
Do it!
求求你
Please.
快点结束  卡西迪奥
End this, Castiel.
小卡  这不是你
Cass... this isn't you.
这不是你
This isn't you.
把石碑拿给我
Bring me the tablet!
小卡
Cass.
我知道你在里面
I know you're in there.
我知道你能听见我
I know you can hear me.
小卡
Cass...
是我啊
It's me.
我们是一家人
We're family.
我们需要你
We need you.
我需要你
I need you.
你必须做出抉择  卡西迪奥
You have to choose, Castiel --
我们  还是他们
Us or them.
小卡
Cass.
卡西迪奥
Castiel!
Castiel!!
小卡
Cass?
不
No.
小卡  小卡
Cass. Cass!
我很抱歉  迪恩
I'm so sorry, Dean.
刚刚怎么回事
What the hell just happened?
你把这里弄成这样  我很喜欢
Love what you've done with the place.
你以为这些能把我永远拦在外面
You really think all that was gonna keep me out forever?
至少够让迪恩和小卡
At least long enough for Dean and Cass
拿到石碑然后离开
to get the tablet and get out.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
原来是他到处插我的孩子
So, that's who's been poking my boys --
还不是性感的那种插
and not in a sexy way.
我得跟你理论理论了  小鹿
Got a bone to pick with you, moose.
看你对我的手下都做了什么
After what you did to my poor dog.
你想把我们说死还是怎么的
You gonna talk us to death or get down to it already?
你一点都没变啊
There's my whore.
但我不是为了那些死人来的
I'm not here for my dearly departed, though.
我为了有奇怪铭文的石头而来
I'm here for the stone with the funny scribbles on it.
你做梦吧
That's not gonna happen.
你放狠话的样子我太喜欢了
Love it when you get all tough.
恰到好处
Touches me right where my bathing suit goes.
快走
Go.
去救你哥哥  和我独一无二的他
Save your brother... and my unicorn.
彭彭和丁满
Timon and Pumbaa...
把大计划都告诉你了
...tell you their big plan?
他们把想法都告诉你了吗
Did they share that little chestnut with you?
他们打算关上地狱之门  宝贝
They mean to close the gates of hell, sweetheart.
他们打算杀了我和所有的恶魔
They mean to kill me and all the demons --
也包括你
You included.
光是那句"杀了我"就够了  克劳力
You had me at "Kill you," Crowley.
这么说  这个娜奥米自从救你出炼狱
So, this "Naomi" has been controlling you
就一直在控制你
since she got you out of purgatory?
是
Yeah.
那是什么打破了这种控制
Well, w-what broke the connection?
我不知道
I don't know.
我现在只知道要保护这块石碑
I just know that I have to protect this tablet now.
防着娜奥米吗
From Naomi?
是
Yes.
还有你
And from you.
我  你在说什么呢
From me? What are you talking about?
小卡
Cass?
Cass!
-见鬼  -迪恩
- Damn it. - Dean!
迪恩
Dean.
小卡在哪
Where's Cass?
消失了
He's gone.
梅格呢
Meg?
我们得走了  立刻
We got to go -- now.
我能揍你到天荒地老
I could beat on you for eternity.
猪头  随便你
Take all the time you want, you pig.
后座上可没有小卡
No Cass in the back seat.
你的石碑早被拿走了
Your stone is long gone.
娜奥米
Naomi.
没想到在这儿见到你
Fancy meeting you here.
好久不见啊
Haven't seen you in a dark age.
我喜欢你的发型
Love the haircut.
你肩膀怎么样了
How's the shoulder?
只是一点皮肉之伤
Just a flesh wound.
我没拿到石碑
Now, I don't have the tablet,
你既然来了  那么你也没拿到
and if you're here, neither do you.
也就是说你的卡西迪奥
Which means that your Castiel
带着我们的东西跑掉了
is in the wind with our prize.
如果我不了解你
If I didn't know you better,
我会说你是身手不行了
I'd say you're losing your touch.
卡西迪奥并没有跑掉
Castiel isn't in the wind.
他在做自己应该做的事
He's doing exactly what he's supposed to do...
保护石碑
Protect the tablet.
连你也防着吗
Even from you?
别激动  亲爱的
Easy, love.
还记得我们在美索不达米亚的时候吗
If you remember our time in Mesopotamia the way I do,
我是个情人  不是斗士
you know I'm a lover, not a fighter.
你到底想怎样  贱货
What do you want, you cockroach?
或许我们可以趁为时不晚  做笔交易
Maybe we can make a deal before this gets truly bollocksed.
我肯定有你想要的东西
I mean, I must have something that you want.
这可是我的专长
Tart stole my move.
那到底是怎么回事
So...what happened?
小卡碰了一下石碑
I mean, Cass touched the tablet,
就被还原成出场设置了
and it reset him to his factory settings or something?
我不知道  我也不在乎
I don't know. And I don't care.
我只知道他带着天堂大规模杀伤性武器跑了
All I know is that he is off the reservation with a-a heavenly WMD.
我不想再听任何人撒谎了
Listen, man, I can't take any more lies...from anyone.
是啊
Yeah.
我懂
I know.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我应该告诉你的
I should have told you.
我只是想相信自己没事
I-I...just wanted to believe I was okay.
我也不知道
I don't know.
你也听到小卡的话了
Well, you heard what Cass said...
第一项测试就把你伤得连他都无法治愈
That that first trial hurt you in ways that even he can't heal.
小萨姆  从现在开始你得对我坦诚
Sammy, I need you to be honest with me from here on out, man.
你说得对
You're right.
我会的
And I will be.
我也许不能承担这些测试
Listen, I may not be able to carry the burden
带来的重担
that comes along with these trials...
但我可以帮你
But I can carry you.
你知道
You...realize
你刚才引用了《指环王》里的话吧
you kind of just quoted "Lord of The Rings", Right?
《指环王》中山姆说"我不能替你承担魔戒  但我可以背你"
而扮演山姆的演员还曾主演《追梦赤子心》中的鲁迪
拜托  那可是山姆啊
Come on, man. But it's the Rudy hobbit, all right?
是一个讲述追梦的励志故事
引用他的话不要紧
Rudy hobbit always gets a pass.
闭嘴
Shut up.